<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Daisy-Head Mayzie | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;The partially finished manuscript for this book was found after Dr. Seuss passed away, and this book was published three years after his death. &lt;em&gt;Daisy-Head Mayzie&lt;/em&gt; is a story of a young girl named Mayzie McGrew who happens to have a daisy sprout out of her head. No one has ever heard of such a thing, and the entire town is in a tizzy. No one knows what to do, until a slick agent named Finagle promises to make Daisy-Head Mayzie a star! She becomes a celebrity, but soon realizes that fame without friends isn’t worth the price. But does anyone still love her? “The job of a daisy is Try and Find out. They love her… They love her not.” The sweet ending shows that while fame and fortune can be fleeting, true family and friends are not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Make a daisy headband. Wrap and measure a flexible strip of cardstock around your child’s head so that it fits snugly. Remove, cut off any excess cardstock, and staple or tape the ends together. Tape or staple a green pipe cleaner (chenille stem) to the back of the headband so that the stem will stick out above your child’s head. Have your child draw a flower on a sheet of paper and cut it out, helping as needed. Tape or staple the flower to the stem. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BR075_DrSeuss_DaisyHead_spread.jpg" alt="Daisy-Head Mayzie Preview" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/seuss4for1sbm.aspx?key=4QFM&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img style="float: right; margin-left: 10px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" border="0" alt="" align="bottom" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=45906</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/BRP/covers/daisy_head_mayzie.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>