<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Hunches in Bunches | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="padding-left: 10px; width: 620px; padding-top: 10px;"&gt;&lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="border-width: 0px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/drseuss/hunches-in-bunches.jpg" alt="Hunches in Bunches Book Cover" /&gt; &lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="border-width: 0px;" src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BRP_HunchesInBunches_annspread.jpg" alt="Hunches in Bunches Preview" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;span id="Blue"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hunches in Bunches&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span class="Heading2"&gt;&lt;span id="Blue"&gt;by Dr. Seuss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p class="normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hunches in Bunches&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is just the book for one of those “What-should-I-do? days” because readers will know that they’re not alone. After all, sometimes it can be awfully hard to decide what to do—especially if you have lots of hunches like the ones brought to life by Dr. Seuss in this classic story. Pointing the way with their fantastical hats, the Happy Hunch, the Sour Hunch, and the Better Hunch (to name a few!) give the narrator lots of ideas. With Seuss’s clever rhyme and amusing illustrations, readers find that it’s better not to follow hunches in bunches impulsively. Instead, the story’s hero talks through all the ideas he has until he arrives at exactly what he wants to do—a way that helps anyone make up their mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="normal"&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Make a “Things-to-Do” jar for those days when your child doesn’t know quite what to do. Sit down with your child and let him think up activities and crafts he enjoys—coloring, building block towers, riding a bike, and so on. Write them down on a piece of paper, and let your child add pictures if he wishes. Then the next time your child says there’s nothing to do, pull out the jar and pick a slip!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/DrSeussBooks.aspx?key=4NZR&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" alt="Join Dr. Seuss Book Club" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=45910</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>