<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>I Can Lick 30 Tigers Today! | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="padding-left: 10px; width: 620px; padding-top: 10px;"&gt;&lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="border-width: 0px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/drseuss/i-can-lick-30-tigers-today.jpg" alt="I Can Lick 30 Tigers Today Book Cover" /&gt; &lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="border-width: 0px;" src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BR083_DrSeuss_Lick30Tigers_spread.jpg" alt="I Can Lick 30 Tigers Today Preview" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;span id="Blue"&gt;&lt;em&gt;I Can Lick 30 Tigers Today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span class="Heading2"&gt;&lt;span id="Blue"&gt;by Dr. Seuss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p class="normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I Can Lick 30 Tigers Today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a trio of terrific stories served up classic Seuss style. In the title story, a boastful young cat wearing a familiar looking hat declares that he can lick 30 tigers today . . . but when he actually has to face 30 tigers, he finds a reason why he might fight only 29, or perhaps 22, and readers will see the perils of bragging. In the next story, King Looie of Katzen-stein decides to have his tail carried ‘round so it doesn’t drag on the ground. But the king’s tail-carrying cat wants his tail carried, too, and so on . . . until the last tail-carrying cat starts a revolution—with “demo-catic” results. And finally, a small cat tells of the time his sister "thunk up a Glunk." She couldn’t "un-thunk" the creature until she worked together with her brother to get rid of it. All together, these cat-tastic stories will make readers a little happier, and perhaps, a little wiser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="normal"&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Try this game the next time your child has a few friends over to play. In a large, open area, give each child a soft scarf to tuck through a belt loop or into pants. Have the children form a line, with each child holding up the scarf of the child in front of him or her. The head of the line won’t be holding a tail, and the child at the end won’t have anyone holding his tail. Have the first child try to lead the line around to try to catch the tail of the last child—making sure that each “cat” in the line doesn’t let go. Allow the children to take turns in different parts of the line.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/DrSeussBooks.aspx?key=4NZR&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" alt="Join Dr. Seuss Book Club" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=45911</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>