<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>My Book About Me | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;This is a book you’re sure to keep, because it’s written by your child (with a little help from co-author Dr. Seuss and illustrator Roy McKie). &lt;em&gt;My Book About Me&lt;/em&gt; asks questions and lets your child fill in the blanks, check off boxes, and draw pictures to tell the world about her likes, dislikes, and lots of other information—creating a written snapshot of who she is. If your child can read and write, she’s sure to love being the “author” of her own book. And even if your child isn’t pencil-ready, she’s sure to delight in telling you all the answers so that you can help her finish the book. Either way, when she’s finished, this first and only edition is one you’re sure to treasure, thanks to your child and Dr. Seuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tie-in Activity: People learn about themselves bit by bit, just like putting a puzzle together. So consider creating a puzzle featuring your child. Print out a large 8" x 10" photo of your child, and glue it to a sturdy piece of cardboard. Then cut it into pieces—in two or three pieces for very young children, more for older children. Your child will have fun putting herself together. Or purchase extra copies of this book to give as birthday presents to your child. That way you’ll have a progression of your child’s self-portrait that you’ll be sure to treasure for years to come. Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:customercare@earlymoments.com"&gt;CustomerCare@EarlyMoments.com&lt;/a&gt; to purchase additional copies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BR080_DrSeuss_BookAboutMe_spread.jpg" alt="My Book About Me Preview" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/seuss4for1sbm.aspx?key=4QFM&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img style="float: right; margin-left: 10px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" border="0" alt="Join Dr. Seuss Book Club" align="bottom" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=45917</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/BRP/covers/my_book_about_me.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>