<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Yertle the Turtle and Other Stories | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;In the classic &lt;em&gt;Yertle the Turtle and Other Stories&lt;/em&gt;, Dr. Seuss shares a trio of cautionary tales—all demonstrating that someone who sets themselves above others is in for an unpleasant surprise. The book begins with Yertle the Turtle, a king who seeks power by climbing on the backs of other turtles—and forgetting about the turtles on the bottom. (A message for all would-be dictators!) It’s followed by the story of vain Gertrude McFuzz, a bird who isn’t happy with her lone tail feather. Finally, a story about a boastful rabbit and bear that are put in their place by a wise worm completes the collection. The expressive illustrations capture the humor and lessons of the stories—&lt;em&gt;Yertle the Turtle and Other Stories&lt;/em&gt; would be a wonderful addition to any bookshelf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Make a turtle! Let your child decorate the bottom of a paper bowl for the turtle’s shell. From green construction paper, you or your child can cut out a large green circle for a head and five triangles for a tail and feet, and glue them to the sides of the bowl.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BR076_DrSeuss_YertleTurtle_spread.jpg" alt="Yertle The Turtle And Other Stories Preview" /&gt; &lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/seuss4for1sbm.aspx?key=4QFM&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img style="float: right; margin-left: 10px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" border="0" alt="" align="bottom" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=45922</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/BRP/covers/yertle_the_turtle.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>