<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>I Can Write! | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;Here is the exception to the often heard rule "don't write in books." Instead, this book gives your child the chance to write a story—with a little help from author Theo. LeSieg (aka Dr. Seuss) and illustrator Roy McKie. Each page of this large-format &lt;strong&gt;Bright and Early&lt;/strong&gt; book includes wide-spaced lines positioned directly underneath the words to encourage a child to copy what he sees. The oversize type and simple words support both early reading and writing skills. And while writing practice isn't always fun, the rollicking rhymes and playful art make this story enjoyable to read and write! In fact, little ones not ready to write will still enjoy listening as you read the story aloud. So whether your child is ready for writing or would simply enjoy listening to a entertaining story, this book is just right for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tie-in Activity: Make writing practice fun: If your child is learning to write, consider putting some flour in a shallow pan so she can "write" with her finger in the flour (shaving cream and fingerpaints are also great materials to use). Little ones also build skills as they scribble with chunky crayons or thick pencils—don't forget to encourage and praise her efforts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BE_ICanWrite_spread.jpg" alt="I Can Write Preview" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/seuss4for1sbm.aspx?key=4QFM&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img style="float: right; margin-left: 10px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" border="0" alt="Join Dr. Seuss Book Club" align="bottom" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=75664</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/BRP/covers/i_can_write.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>