<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>The 500 Hats of Bartholomew Cubbins | Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;Told in prose, this book was among the earliest written and illustrated by Dr. Seuss. This classic tale features beautifully detailed black-and-white drawings highlighted with the bright red hats of the hero, Bartholomew Cubbins. Why so many hats? Even Bartholomew doesn't know. It all starts when he can't remove his hat in front of King Derwin, because each time he does another hat appears on his head! The suspense builds in this amusing story as everyone the king asks, from wise men to the Royal Executioner, fails to remove Bartholomew's hat (luckily for Bartholomew!). Bartholomew and King Derwin are able to strike a deal that makes them both happy, though neither can ever explain "what happened to happen" with Bartholomew's hats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tie-in Activity: Gather as many different hats as you can: winter hats, baseball caps, floppy sun hats, and so on. Sit with your baby in front of a mirror and place the hats on his head, letting your child take them on or off. For an older child, ask him to try and keep as many hats on his head as possible as you read the story aloud. See how many are left by the end of the story.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/NextBook/BRU/BRP_500HatsOfBartCubbins_spread.jpg" alt="The 500 Hats of Bartholomew Cubbins Preview" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/seuss4for1sbm.aspx?key=4QFM&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="_Blank"&gt;&lt;img style="float: right; margin-left: 10px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/green_arrow.gif" border="0" alt="" align="bottom" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=75665</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/BRP/covers/bartholomew_500_hats.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-08-06</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>