<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Aladdin and the Dancing Princess | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/aladdin_dancing_princess.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aladdin and the Dancing Princess&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this delightful Disney variation, a Mickey Mouse version of Aladdin visits his esteemed desert friend, the sultan. When the sultan confesses his worries about his daughter’s nighttime escapades, Mickey offers to guard the tower where she sleeps. Sure enough, he witnesses the beautiful princess escaping from the tower at midnight to ride off with a handsome prince for a night of dancing. When Mickey confronts the princess the next morning, she tearfully confesses her love for the prince, and her fear that her father would never allow them to wed. Mickey offers to talk to the sultan, who ultimately agrees to bless his daughter’s marriage to her beloved prince. This happy tale features themes of loyalty, honesty, and love against all odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Illustrate the importance of open communication between parent and child by encouraging him to share his thoughts, feelings, and emotions when he's not allowed to take part in an activity. For example, if he asks to cross the street by himself, acknowledge his desire by asking him to describe what he thinks it would be like, and then explain why it's in his best interests to cross with you until he's older. Point out some activities that your child can do independently that he couldn't when he was younger, such as picking out what shirt to wear or feeding himself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/2/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89608</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>