<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>A White Christmas | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/white_christmas.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A White Christmas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this heartwarming holiday tale, some of the most beloved Disney characters all want the same thing for Christmas: to escape from the dismal rain. Huey, Dewey, and Louie are desperate for some snow, while Mickey Mouse dreams of a sunny beach vacation. As they plan their respective trips, they look out the window and are delighted to see that the rain has turned to snow. Huey, Dewey, and Louie head outside for sledding and snowball fights with Goofy. Back at Uncle Donald’s, with Goofy in tow, the boys are thrilled to see the tree beautifully decorated. They decide not to go to the mountains after all, and call Mickey and Minnie to invite them to join them. On Christmas Day, the whole gang reunites for an old-fashioned white Christmas, complete with eggnog and ice-skating. They realize there’s no place like home after all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Help your child brainstorm a list of fun things to do at home on a rainy day. The exercise will help him learn to appreciate the comforts of home and come up with imaginative (and economical) ways to stay entertained.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/2/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89606</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>