<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Alice in Wonderland | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/alice_in_wonderland.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alice in Wonderland&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more than 130 years, the famous Lewis Carroll classic has sparked the imaginations of children of all ages. With Walt Disney’s delightful re-telling, even the best-known details are made new again with vivid illustrations and magical verses. Kids will come face-to-face with the same curious cast of characters we all remember from the original, including the Mad Hatter, the White Rabbit, and the Cheshire Cat. Perhaps the most imaginative children’s story ever told, Disney’s &lt;em&gt;Alice in Wonderland&lt;/em&gt; encourages young readers to suspend their expectations and embrace the unusual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Host your own “Mad Tea Party” at home. Encourage kids to come dressed in their choice of crazy ensemble, complete with an outrageous hat. Suspend regular table etiquette and make nonsense the order of the day, with everyone speaking in silly rhymes and breaking out into spontaneous song. Whenever possible, do things backwards: serve tea in bowls instead of cups, put plates upside-down, and put napkins on your heads instead of in your laps.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/2/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89611</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>