<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Donald Duck and the Magic Stick | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/donald_duck_magic_stick.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Donald Duck and the Magic Stick&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Young readers will be entranced by this magical tale, laced with valuable lessons regarding the power of having faith in the unknown. The story begins with Donald sending his nephews off for apprenticeship in a trade. Huey and Dewey are the first to complete their training, and are presented with magical items from each of their teachers. On their return trip home, an evil innkeeper steals their magic gifts and replaces them with items that hold no powers. When the boys show what they believe are magic items to Donald, he scoffs and mocks the boys for their foolishness. Louie then recovers the magic items from the innkeeper using a magic stick he received during his woodcutting apprenticeship. When he puts on a spectacular show, doubting Donald soon discovers that he believes in magic after all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Using the magical gifts from the story as inspiration, encourage your child to invent magical powers for toys, books, or other household items. For example, she could have a magic toy box that picks up toys, a book that would read and turn pages, or a refrigerator that magically fills with food. Then, embrace her artistic talents by helping her draw her magic inventions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/2/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89643</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>