<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>How to Catch a Heffalump | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="padding-left: 10px; width: 620px; padding-top: 10px;"&gt;&lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="border-width: 0px;" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DBC/1/heffalump.jpg" alt="Disney Book Title" /&gt; &lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/3/green_arrow.gif" alt="Join Disney Book Club" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Catch a Heffalump&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a menacing trumpeting noise fills the Hundred Acre Wood, the animals who live there are alerted to the presence of the scary Heffalumps. Although Rabbit, Tigger, Pooh, and Piglet have never actually seen a Heffalump, they’ve heard all about their reputations as vicious, wild beasts. When young Roo suggests setting out on a journey to catch the very first Heffalump, the group agrees, although it’s Roo who eventually ends up befriending Lumpy, a baby Heffalump who is frustrated at not being taken seriously by the older members of his family. When the other animals attempt to capture Lumpy, Roo rises to his defense. Children of all ages can benefit from the underlying message that people are not always what they seem, and that the greatest friendships are based on respect for one another’s differences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Have your child use crayons to draw a picture of themselves, choosing appropriate colors for their hair, eyes and skin tone. Then have them draw a picture of their best friend. Talk to them about differences and what makes every child unique and individual. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89668</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>