<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Meet the Robinsons | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 10px"&gt;&lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="BORDER-TOP-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-LEFT-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-BOTTOM-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-RIGHT-WIDTH: 0px" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DBC/1/meettherobinsons.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/3/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meet the Robinsons &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this creative and inspirational book, we meet 12-year-old Lewis, an orphan and amateur inventor who wants nothing more than to recapture his memories of his mother. When he meets a boy named Wilbur Robinson at a science fair, Wilbur offers to bring Lewis along to the year 2037 in his time machine. Lewis agrees in hopes that he’ll later be able to go back in time and find his mother. In the future, Lewis meets an eccentric cast of characters, fights evil ones who have followed him there, and ultimately finds himself in a position to save the world as he knows it. With plenty of zany plot twists and turns, this rich story reinforces the importance of belonging, the intricacy of family, and the need to persevere to overcome obstacles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Help your child create a family tree as a visual mapping of his ancestry. Start with your immediate family and branch out into grandparents, cousins, uncles, aunts, and second cousins. For younger children, let them draw pictures of these family members. Mount the completed family tree on his bedroom wall as a constant reminder of the importance of family.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89676</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>