<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>The Fairy Without Wings | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 10px"&gt;&lt;img id="ctl00_fullRegion_mainAndRightRegion_Image1" style="BORDER-TOP-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-LEFT-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-BOTTOM-WIDTH: 0px; BORDER-RIGHT-WIDTH: 0px" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DBC/1/fairywithoutwings.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/4/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Fairy Without Wings &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the delightful &lt;em&gt;Disney Fairies&lt;/em&gt; series, this story chronicles the adventures of Rani, a fairy who chose to give up her wings in exchange for the safety of Mother Dove. Rani now struggles with feelings of insecurity and inadequacy without her wings. She turns to a group of mermaids for comfort, swimming in their lagoon and striving to become one of them. In spite of her determination to belong, she soon finds out that her true friends are those from her fairy life, and that they love her unconditionally, with or without her wings. This inspirational tale encourages young readers to value themselves just as they are and to resist passing judgment on others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: During your next outdoor excursion, gather up some sticks, bark, pussy willow branches, rocks, feathers, pinecones, and other materials and create an all-natural fairy house. Attach your findings to a shoe box. Be sure to cut out a door so the fairies can come and go as they please. Explain to your child that her favorite fairies can use the house as a refuge during the next storm.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89726</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>