<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>The Little Mermaid and Spot | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/little_mermaid_and_spot.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Little Mermaid and Spot&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone’s favorite mermaid returns in this charming spinoff of Disney’s classic, &lt;em&gt;The Little Mermaid&lt;/em&gt;. Ariel and her sidekick Flounder are joined by an adorable baby whale, Spot, who loves playing catch. During one of their games, the ball accidentally hits Crabby, a small, grumpy crab with a big temper. The crab refuses to accept Ariel’s apology. Later, when Spot bumps into King Triton and causes him to drop his trident, it accidentally turns Crabby into a giant monster crab. Crabby captures Ariel and puts her in a cage, convinced she and Spot were picking on him. Later, he steals the trident and shrinks King Triton to a tiny size. Spot saves the day by chaining Crabby up and reclaiming the trident. By the end of the story, everyone is back to their regular size, Crabby has apologized, and Spot is the hero of the day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Ask your child to think of a time when they rose to someone’s defense, or when someone else stood up for them. Make your child aware of the harmful impacts of bullying, and outline a procedure to follow in the event that they are victimized.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/4/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89742</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>