<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress>&lt;p&gt;The secret world of the fairies of Pixie Hollow is revealed in this enchanting tale about everyone’s favorite fairy, Tinker Bell. In a story sprinkled with the magic of pixie dust, we follow Tinker Bell as her natural curiosity leads her to investigate a fairy house built by a human. Because fairies must never be seen by humans, fellow fairy Vidia tries to teach Tink a lesson. But things go wrong, and Tinker Bell is discovered by a fairy-loving little girl named Lizzie!&amp;nbsp; Based on the Disney feature &lt;em&gt;Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue,&lt;/em&gt; this heartwarming story shows us the power of friendship—and helps us understand that some things aren’t meant to be seen, just believed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color: #ca2d92;"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Try to build your own fairy house. A fairy house can be built in a quiet, protected yard, park, beach or other natural area. Start by gathering up some natural materials—such as sticks, dried grasses and leaves, pinecones, and so on. Don’t disturb animal nests or pick live plants. And be sure not to gather up poison ivy or similar plants. (Fairies don’t like it, and neither will you.) Start constructing the walls by placing similar-sized short sticks in the ground, add a roof, and then add any decorative elements you like. Be on the lookout for fairies!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</ingress>
  <text>&lt;table style="width: 546px;"&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td width="33%" align="left" valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89854"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Games/tile1-TBGreatFairy.jpg" border="0" alt="Puzzles &amp;amp; Games" width="169" height="168" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td width="34%" align="center" valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89856"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Games/tile2-TBGreatFairy.jpg" border="0" alt="Coloring Pages" width="169" height="168" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td width="33%" align="right" valign="top"&gt;&lt;a href="/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89855"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Games/tile3-TBGreatFairy.jpg" border="0" alt="Fun Activities" width="169" height="168" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p style="font-family: Arial,Helvetica,sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: #608e50; text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click on one of the tiles above to have more fun with Tinker Bell.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/2/green_arrow.gif" alt="Join Disney Book Club" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89761</url><image1>/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/tinkerbell_fairy_rescue.jpg</image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>