<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <projectCode />
  <productNumber>XXX00000000</productNumber>
  <title>The Aristocats | Disney Book Club by Early Moments</title>
  <ingress></ingress>
  <text>&lt;div class="nextbook" style="PADDING-LEFT: 10px; WIDTH: 620px; PADDING-TOP: 30px"&gt;&lt;img style="BORDER-RIGHT: white 15px solid; BORDER-TOP: white 15px solid; FLOAT: right; BORDER-LEFT: white 15px solid; BORDER-BOTTOM: white 15px solid" alt="Disney Book Title" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/DisneyRelaunch/aristocats.jpg" /&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="Heading1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Aristocats&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Young readers will be captivated by this imaginative tale of animal camaraderie, adventure, and good versus evil. Based on the renowned 1970 Disney animated film, this story centers around a pampered housecat, Duchess, and her three kittens, Marie, Berlioz, and Toulouse. Duchess and her kittens stand to inherit the fortunes of their retired opera star owner, Madame Bonafamille. When the Madame’s villainous butler, Edgar, attempts to cheat the feline family out of their inheritance by cat-napping the pampered brood and releasing them in the streets of Paris, his plan is foiled with the help of a streetwise tomcat and other animal accomplices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="COLOR: #ca2d92"&gt;Tie-in Activity: Expose your child to the Parisian culture by sharing a book or CD that introduces the French language using simple phrases and numbers. Incorporate different parts of the culture by serving international foods or visiting an art museum to see work by French artists. For added fun, you and your child could even adopt a French name during pretend play.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="https://orders.earlymoments.com/disneymagnix.aspx?key=4PE5&amp;amp;VendorCode=EMS1" target="”_Blank”"&gt;&lt;img alt="Join Disney Book Club" src="/upload/EarlyMoments/Art/3/green_arrow.gif" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<format /><visible>false</visible><weight /><available /><priority /><recommendedAge /><url>/Templates/Default/Pages/Article.aspx?id=89918</url><image1></image1></text>
  <image2 />
  <thumbnail />
  <created>2009-10-11</created>
  <removed />
  <published />
  <ageCategories />
</product>